[snorts]
Zach, when you look at why y'all lost
this one, what's the biggest reason?
It's
>> tough. It was It was a strange game,
obviously.
Uh to give them 14 points. Um we felt
like we had pretty good control early in
the game and had a chance to really, you
know, create a lot of separation and
gave them 14 points. Then the defense
gives up six total, you know, two field
goals and and that's got to be enough to
win. And um you know, you just look at
there there's little things that got us.
We've missed two extra points. We had
two turnovers for touchdowns. Um, and
then they had a two-minute drive to win
the game. And it's just frustrating and
it's it's it's just frustrating. That's
the biggest thing. And then that we
weren't able just to finish it in some
area, finish that game and and uh find a
way to get a win.
>> What did you tell team?
>> Yeah, that's it's a little bit fitting
to be honest with you in in terms of how
our season's gone. And um it doesn't
make it right. Doesn't make it.
just, you know,
several times we we've had games where
we played well in different areas and we
just we just haven't found a way to to
put it all together and and there's been
games these last couple weeks we had. Uh
but this is one we needed to finish off,
you know, a divisional game and this is
this is how these divisional games go
and it usually comes down to a to a play
at the end.
>> What was your
>> one score game and we just we weren't
able to finish off. What was your view
of kind of what Cleveland was able to do
to be successful on their final play?
>> Well, I mean, they they hit a couple
throws over there in the flat and and
got a couple chunks and I thought we did
a good job stopping them for two plays
and then and then they get the one that
would just kind of get them, you know,
10 yards and get up closer and put them
in field goal range and and their kicker
did a great job finishing off.
>> What do [snorts] you think it's been
this year about not being able to close
out games? Like you said, common theme.
there's something that you feel [snorts]
like going into the offseason that you
can
>> that's something we're gonna have to
look you know to to sit here today and
do that answer um is challenging and and
so reflect back obviously obviously we
had the answer we would have pulled it
today um so that's just something we got
to really look at.
>> Was there a thought of I know you needed
the touchdown but was there a thought of
taking more time off the clock? Um
>> it's hard. Yeah, there's always Yeah,
you'd love to score with one second
left, but it's it's challenging if you
if you run it and you waste a down on a
zero yard gain just just for the sake of
running the clock. It's challenging. So,
um we've been in that situation a lot or
sometimes we don't score on the first
play and we do that. Um let's get points
on the board, go get a stop and win the
game. It just didn't work out.
>> What makes it so tough that defense when
you're
>> incredibly tough? I mean, he's he's the
best player in in on the defense side of
the ball. He's the best player and he
wrecks every single play. you got to
account for them. Um they got a really
good defensive line. They got a really
good defense around. I'm not going to
just minimize it and say it's a good
defensive line. It's a really good
defense. Um that's been challenging for
every team they've played all season.
You know, you just look at these last
couple games they've played. Um they're
they do a great job. They they make it
hard. You got to earn everything. I
thought we we found some success at
different points in the game and and um
[snorts] you know, just weren't able to
score more than the the 18 or whatever
we scored. Having a year that, you know,
you guys have had to ending of this
game, you know, the defense has a chance
to, you know, make a play, end the
season on on a high note. What kind of a
taste does it leave just, you know,
having it end the way that it has so
many times?
>> Yeah, not a good one. Not a good taste.
Do
>> you have a long conversation with the
officials after the Garrett sack? What
was going on there? What were you
>> We're trying. There's five minutes left
in our season. We're playing for our
lives here and I was never told that
we're going to stop the game. And in a
critical moment like that and the refs
just said that they made a decision that
they were going to stop the game and
they said they tried to do it as quickly
as possible. I I didn't feel that. Um we
didn't sub. We're trying to be on the
ball and go and play with tempo and the
umpire just held the ball so that we
couldn't do anything. And I'm yelling at
Joe, get on the ball. We didn't sub.
We're going and that we couldn't play.
And so again, trying to get an answer
was not easy. Um they just said that
they made a decision as a as a crew to
stop the game when that happened. I
guess it didn't matter when it happened.
It just they were going to stop the game
and let it happen.
>> And you weren't informed of that.
>> No, I was never informed of that. They
didn't say one word. We meet with them
in the 90-minute meeting before the
game. They didn't they never said one
word about that.
>> How did you uh kind of did you approach
this like a normal game for Burrow in
terms of week 18? You obviously played
the full share of reps.
>> Yes. Yes, we we we played that game to
win the game and and every decision we
made and um you know, I know what was
made of the the sack record and and um
he's earned that. He he has earned that.
He He's earned that because
um and I say that because we we weren't
we weren't saying we we don't want to
walk out of here without him break. We
we just wanted to win the game, so we're
going to call whatever we did to win it.
And um but to his credit, I mean the the
guy never he rarely has one-on- ones
ever. Ever ever. And um so for him to be
able to do that and get that record um I
didn't track the other times those
records were broken, but this was
unbelievable that he was able to do that
with with everything that is put on him
in the tape and minimized and um they
don't play with leads, you know,
typically. I'm not trying to take a shot
on him. That's just the truth of it this
year. So um that's a credit to him, man.
He's he's earned that.
>> Why did you choose to bring Flacko in on
the quarterback?
>> Um just bigger body there. They they
were really loading up the front. If you
saw some of those short yardage plays
and Flaco's obviously a much bigger body
>> had some rhythm there on the the drive
that put y'all ahead late. What kind of
maybe enabled y'all to have the rhythm
there late in the second half that you
maybe didn't earlier in the half?
>> I don't think we had a lot of
possessions really. You know, I think
that was I don't know what possession
that was in the drive. We had one in the
third quarter if I remember correctly
and finished, you know, the quarter
ended with one and um so it just it
didn't didn't feel like there was we had
a lot of plays in the second half. We
had a bunch in the first half and and
not as many in the second half.
>> Chase Brown, Zack went over a thousand
yards rushing today. He also caught a
touchdown pass. Is he one of the very
biggest highlights for you from
>> Yeah, he he I thought he had an
outstanding season and very dependable
for us. Um has really worked hard to be
the player that he is and so for the
production to match that. I'm really
proud of Chase. Um proud of the guys up
front, you know, that have helped pave
the way for those rushing yards. proud
of Justin Hill. You know, Justin's done
a great job getting that room, getting
getting the nera full potential.
So, I was I obviously these these
milestones and achievements are are uh
bittersweet when when it happens like
this, but at the same time, when a
player puts a lot into his work and his
craft and his career, and uh you're
happy to see them to reach those
milestones that will be with them
forever. I know you've suggested this or
hinted at this before, but how confident
are you that there's enough brain power
in the building, both coaching staff,
administration, all of it together to
make sure this doesn't happen next year?
>> I'm very confident.
>> Why? Wh Why do you
>> We have really good people and I enjoy
working with them and um this stings all
of us equally and I just I trust
everybody.
>> Certainly a great season. Didn't miss an
extra point.
>> I I missed.
Um how how unusual is that to see him
just two extra points although I know
one was tipped but how unusual was that
cuz
>> Yeah. Well I mean you I think you got to
factor that in. One was tipped and um
the second one to be truthful I I don't
I don't have any answer for you right
now.
>> But when the seasons end what what are
the conversations usually like with the
front office with y'all as you kind of
get ready for
>> I just keep those private to ourselves.
>> Is there any long-term concern?
Obviously DJ with tap
>> no not not long term. No none of them
are longterm. Um that's all that
matters. Is there is there any
frustration from kind of a staff and a
team that you know you guys have had,
you know, put up a lot of points against
Pittsburgh, a lot against Baltimore, but
Cleveland seems to be that one team you
can't seem to that you seem to struggle
[clears throat] against more than most
others. Does it kind of get frustrating
knowing obviously they have Miles
obviously that defensive front, but is
there, you know, just kind of some
frustration that that seems to be like
the one team that's just hard to crack?
>> No, I think um I think a lot of teams
have a hard time scoring and moving the
ball against them. we'd beaten him the
last four times and we had a really
great opportunity to beat him again
today for a fifth time. So, um,
sometimes in this league it's not always
pretty and I wish we scored 50 every
game and the production was outstanding,
but but there's also times you go in and
give a lot of respect to your opponent
and they've earned that and they've made
it really challenging on everybody
including us. Um, so I know that, you
know, we always feel that and our fan
base feels that, but so does so does
every team that walks into Cleveland and
plays against them and um, you know, we
just we didn't find enough enough ways
to score today to be able to separate
ourselves.
>> What do the next 24 hours look like for
you?
>> Meet with a lot of players. You know,
that's it's the exit day for those guys.
So, we'll have a team meeting in the
morning. Um, they'll do their physicals.
They'll get with their position coaches
and myself as much as I can. And um, and
then we'll let them be on their way. As
you move forward beyond this season,
what does it mean to you to have the
support of Burrow and Chase?
>> Yeah, it's we work really hard on the
relationships. Those are more important
things and we want those guys to trust
us. You know, we we work really hard to
put them in great positions so that they
can get the most out of out of their
abilities and help our team win. And I
think that they see that and they
respect that. And the only way we can we
can reach our potential with those two
guys is if you got a relationship to
match it where um you pour into them and
they know that you're you want the best
for them and um I've worked really hard
with those two guys as our coaches have
and and they've reciprocated that. And
so, um,
it's a hard thing to do because you face
a lot of adversity, you know, as a group
and and you go through a lot of ups and
downs and to do it with those guys is,
uh, it's special because of how hard
they work and how much it means to them.
And so, I think to be a part of that, I
don't take it for granted, um, is
something we work real hard at.
Okay. Thank you.